[ Watch on kissFlix.co ]
Who the hell is it?
Let me tell you, it's the middle of the night.
Quit playing tricks on me!
I am a martial artist.
Back in elementary school, I won
1st prize in a city martial arts contest.
I've written two martial arts manuals.
Seven or eight guys can't even touch me.
So what if you're a wild beast?
Jackals, bears...
Even if you're a tiger...
I'll kill you in three punches!
Try me if you don't believe it.
You think I'm...
A real tiger?!
Bro, I was just bluffing earlier, bro!
Mr. Fang, you... run!
I'll hold it off!
Bie Fan!
Just leave me!
I've figured it out.
Getting killed by a tiger is still dying.
Not a bad way to go. You leave!
Come here!
Come chase me!
Chase me!
Bie Fan!
Come here, tiger. Look at me!
Today, either you kill me...
...or I kill you!
Come on!
I'm talking to you! Answer me!
Don't provoke it!
Are you deaf?
You can't... You can't die! Eat me!
It's settled! Eat me!
His meat doesn't taste good!
Eat me! Come on!
He's over fifty!
I'm young! My meat is tasty!
Young meat is tough!
Listen to me, tiger.
Listen to me, tiger!
Can you just shut up?
Eat me!
I'm trying really hard to save you!
I'll kick you to death!
You... Can't you...
...hear me?
Don't listen to him!
Come here!
I don't think it understands.
I'll hit you.
Mr. Fang.
Thank you.
What are you doing here?
I was afraid you'd kill yourself.
So I followed... kept following you.
I was afraid you'd kill yourself,
so I just kept following you.
You still have a friend.
Bie Fan.
Thanks.
You...
Didn't you already kiss that girl?
Why did she leave?
Mr. Fang!
Bro, eat some fruit.
I'm telling you.
I'm not done with that tiger.
To hell with it!
Why is it so sour?
The more I eat, the hungrier I get.
What kind of fruit is this?
I don't know. I picked it up nearby.
Jumping off a building didn't kill me.
The tiger didn't kill me.
But now I'm getting poisoned by a chef!
Mr. Fang!
My stomach hurts!
Help!
Why yell? There's no one around here.
How could anyone possibly save us?
We still have to yell!
We're going to die out here!
Fang Haowen!
My stomach hurts!
Is anyone there?
Haozi!
Why are you here?
I saw the news about you online.
I was terrified something happened to you.
Bought a ticket yesterday and flew over.
I've been looking for you day and night.
I finally found you.
When we parted ways last time, I thought
I'd never see you again in this lifetime.
It hurts!
Son.
What's wrong?
Mom.
Mom!
Yue'er, let me tell you...
I was tricked.
Tricked how?
She per...
She personally told me.
She said,
she said she appreciated my talent,
then turned around and sold me out.
After everything I've been through,
I feel so wronged.
No one can understand me.
Haozi, from today on,
I'll always be by your side.
No matter what
hardships you face in life,
or any pain,
I'll be with you.
You'll be with me?
What about your husband?
We broke up.
Broke up?
Then what about the baby you're carrying?
Actually, I've always wanted to tell you.
This baby is...
Is...
Catch me! Catch me and I'll tell you!
Come catch me! Come catch me!
Haozi.
Come catch me!
Where did you go?
Come on! Catch me!
Come on!
Mom.
I think I messed up.
I fed Mr. Fang a poisonous fruit.
He... Look.
He looks like he's dying.
Silly kid, it's fine.
Look, isn't Mr. Fang alive and kicking?
Yue'er,
the baby you're carrying is...
Is...
Is really...
Looks like Mr. Fang is starving.
Yue'er.
His lips are a bit chapped.
They scratched me till I bled.
Yue'er, you go first.
I...
Go!
Come at me if you have the guts.
Let my wife and unborn child go.
Come on!
Scared? Let's go one-on-one!
You ate my wife and child!
I'm taking you down!
Go for my throat, huh?
Go for my throat!
I'll hit you with a body slam!
Bam, I'll flip you over!
Believe me?
Are you scared?
Spit my wife and child out!
Spit them out!
Freeze!
Evil beast, do not harm people!
Master, hurry!
Look.
Patron, sorry to startle you.
I must be dreaming. I'm... dreaming.
You... You...
I...
Where's that... where's that tiger?
My wife and kid are still in its belly!
Where did that tiger go? That tiger!
Don't panic, Patron.
Everything is but an illusion.
Patron, this humble monk is from
the Great Tang of the East.
To meet you eminent monks...
This...
What an honor!
Please rise, Patron.
I... I want to ask,
are you heading to the Western Heaven?
Can you take me with you?
I can't stay here anymore.
I've suffered too many hardships.
Please take me with you.
Please, Tang Monk?
Patron.
Life is full of hardships.
It is a path we all must walk.
If you persevere,
you will eventually achieve fulfillment.
Master is right!
I can't persevere anymore!
Right now, I just want to die.
I just want to die!
Tang Monk, take me to the Western Heaven.
But, Patron,
this humble monk's disciples
all have terminal illnesses.
No,
have unique skills.
What extraordinary abilities do you have?
I am but a man of letters.
Wukong, let's go.
Let's go.
Wait, wait, wait!
Okay, don't go. Don't go!
Okay, alright, alright.
We're not going, not going.
Look, I'm just a mortal.
But you're immortals.
I just have two small requests.
Could you help me out?
Very simple. First,
my wife and kid were eaten by a tiger.
Could you bring my wife and kid
back for me?
And one more thing.
There's a cabin on that mountain.
Inside is a White Bone Demon.
Could you grab her while you're at it?
Patron,
this humble monk cannot bring them back.
What's done cannot be undone.
Aren't you Victorious Fighting Buddha
and Marshal Tianpeng?
You can't even help with this?
We haven't got the True Scriptures yet.
Doesn't Sun Wukong know
the Seventy-Two Transformations?
Just transform my wife and kid back.
That should do it.
What's wrong?
Transform!
What the hell? So disgusting!
Get lost!
Man, this Idiot is so demanding.
Who are you calling an Idiot?
You're immortals.
What's wrong with helping out?
Why are you spouting gossip
over there?
Don't be insolent!
Who's being insolent?
How dare you speak so arrogantly!
I did. Gonna hit me?
You Scoundrel! Take a blow from my cudgel!
Stop bragging!
Bring it on, Stable Boy!
Hit me right here! Come on!
Hit me here if you have guts! So annoying!
Who do you think you are? Fight me!
I dare you to touch me!
Senior Brother, don't hit! Don't touch me!
Let's talk this out!
Senior Brother!
Second Senior Brother is right.
Wukong, don't be impulsive.
Nothing a vegetarian meal can't solve.
He is a mortal.
He can't understand your struggles.
Right!
I'm a mortal.
You immortals, give me a hand.
So what if I'm a mortal?
So what if you're immortals?
Especially you!
A lustful, greedy, backstabbing pig!
And a hot-tempered monkey!
So annoying!
Stop acting like a Phony!
Who are you lecturing here?
Who are you putting on an act for?
Where do you get the nerve to act with me?
Freeze!
Beat him up!
Wujing, you hit a bit too hard just now.
Watching it made my heart skipped a beat.
He doesn't value me at all.
When he insulted my senior brothers,
he didn't bring me up at all!
It doesn't matter if he brings you up.
Just remember to bring the luggage.
That monkey beat me up.
The pig beat me up.
Sha Monk beat me up too.
Are we done here?
Hello.
Please, calm down.
Do not let a moment's humiliation
disturb your mind.
I am Confucius, Kong Zhongni.
Kong Zhongni?
Why are you pretending to be Confucius?
I am Zhuangzi.
Zhuangzi?
Why don't you claim to be Sun Tzu?
I am Sun Tzu.
Then are we missing Laozi?
I am Laozi.
You really cleared my meridians.
No, what are you doing?
Do I even know you?
Dazzling white.
You're a white... white-bearded old man.
You're dazzling white, you really are...
A gentleman remains steadfast in adversity.
A petty person becomes reckless in poverty.
The humiliation of cyberbullying,
The pain of heartbreak,
Are all earthly illusions.
You must govern by non-action.
Heartbreak is like facing an enemy.
Treat it like commanding an army.
It's an opportunity to temper your mind.
Follow the course of nature,
Avoid the enemy's edge,
And do not cling to pain.
Engage actively with the world.
Roam freely in the world,
and gather your strength.
By not contending, one is beyond contention.
You must...
Oh my God!
Don't give me that!
Stop pretending to be...
Confucius, Laozi, Zhuangzi, and Sun Tzu!
What's this got to do with you, Sadako?
Go back!
Scram, scram, scram!
Bie Fan
Did you run into the tiger too?
No.
Do you like the starry sky too?
I'm Fang Haowen.
A man of letters.
We're fellow artists.
I'm Vincent van Gogh.
Who?
Vincent van Gogh.
Vin... Vin...
You're Vincent van Gogh?
Oh my God! I get to meet Vincent van Gogh!
And it seems I can... can understand you.
Your ear.
Where's my ear?
A tiger took it.
What about your ear?
I cut it off for the woman I love.
She must've been very touched.
No.
She told me to get lost.
W-why did you give her your ear?
I wanted her to hear my heart.
Then she should've given you hers.
I didn't think of that.
You know me?
I do. But not just me.
It's not just me who knows you.
The whole world knows you.
They love you.
They're all crazy about you.
But when I was alive...
Why didn't anyone love me?
What do they love about me?
They love your paintings.
Do you remember painting one...
called Sunflowers?
It sold for 100 million last year.
US dollars.
That could buy a lot of leather shoes.
Before, my paintings
couldn't even buy a bag of potatoes.
They took my *The Potato Eaters*
and hung it in the bathroom.
At least they still bought your paintings.
I sold one painting for 400 francs.
Do you know why?
Why?
Because the buyer was drunk.
They have drunkards abroad too?
Quite a few drunkards, actually.
He must've made a fortune by now.
Let me ask you something.
Since
your paintings couldn't buy potatoes,
why did you keep painting?
Because these colors screamed in my veins.
If I didn't paint them,
they'd split my bones
and burst through my skin.
What about you?
Why do you write books?
Can your books buy you potatoes?
The moon is a triangle.
You found me.
Who are you?
Tencent Video.
Why are you airing this show?
Because we want to bring the audience joy.
Can you?
We can. Look at the danmaku.
Dan-what?
Danmaku.
Thank you.
It's been over 130 years.
You're the only one who'll listen to me.
This gift is for you.
This...
You're not giving me a painting?
The truth is, I don't have much
to give you.
Then give me a poem.
You got it.
Some write poetry with passion,
stopping purely at the level of feeling.
Yet it makes water drops surge
and flames burn fiercely.
Some
write poetry with talent.
Before they even try,
their words are already lofty,
stunningly arrogant.
Some
write poetry with their brains,
shrewdly manipulating words.
Every sentence is twisted into poetry
before it's allowed on stage.
Some
write poetry with their hearts.
Unbearable joy and pain
are, in the process,
completely dissolved.
No matter how fierce the impulse,
it ultimately returns to calm.
Some, since they began writing poetry,
grow thinner day by day.
Every single word
is mass torn from their bodies.
People like this write poetry
with their lives.
Oh no, I'm out of tune.
I can't hear you! I can't hear you!
I can't hear you!
Mom.
You're drooling.
Why is there so much?
You can't see me. Can't... can't see me.
You can't see me.
M- Mr. Fang.
Yeah.
Run!
Hurry up!
Calm down!
Mr. Fang, is that long thing a bug?
What bug? It's poop.
Did you poop that?
What would I even poop out?
Have I even eaten anything?
To be able to poop that much?
That's not my poop!